<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?> 
<Quotes>
  <Quote id="1">
    <Text>"It is not the strongest of the species that survives, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change"</Text>
    <Author>Charles Darwin</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="2">
    <Text>"The secret of fast progress is inefficiency, fast and furious and numerous failures."</Text>
    <Author>Kevin Kelly</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="3">
    <Text>"Experiment fearlessly!"</Text>
    <Author>Tom Peters</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="4">
    <Text>"You can't be a serious innovator unless and until you are ready, willing and able to seriously play. 'Serious play' is not an oxymoron; it is the essence of innovation."</Text>
    <Author></Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="5">
    <Text>"You miss hundred percent of the shots you never take"</Text>
    <Author>Wayne Gretzky</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="6">
    <Text>"I think it is very important for you to do two things: act on your temporary conviction as if it was a real conviction; and when you realize that you are wrong, correct course very quickly."</Text>
    <Author>Andy Grove</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="7">
    <Text>"How do I know what I think until I see what I say."</Text>
    <Author>C.K Chesterton</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="8">
    <Text>"This is so simple it sounds stupid, but it is amazing how few oil people really understand that you only find oil if you drill wells. You may think you're finding it when you're drawing maps and studying logs, but you have to drill."</Text>
    <Author>John Masters</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="9">
    <Text>"Natural selection is death. ... Without huge amounts of death, organisms do not change over time. ... Death is the mother of structure. ... It took four billion years of death ... to invent the human mind ..."</Text>
    <Author></Author>
  </Quote>
   <Quote id="10">
    <Text>"When the good gets going, the going gets good!"</Text>
    <Author>Vijay</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="11">
    <Text>"Companies have defined so much 'best practice' that they are more or less identical"</Text>
    <Author>Jesper Kunde</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="12">
    <Text>"Some people look for things that went wrong and try to fix them. I look for things that went right, and try to build off them."</Text>
    <Author>Bob Stone</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="13">
    <Text>"Never doubt that a small group of committed people can change the world. Indeed it is the only thing that ever has."</Text>
    <Author>Margaret Mead</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="14">
    <Text>"We have a 'strategic plan.' It's called doing things."</Text>
    <Author>Herb Kelleher</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="15">
    <Text>"Intelligent people can always come up with intelligent reasons to do nothing."</Text>
    <Author>Scott Simon</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="16">
    <Text>"Whenever anything is being accomplished, I have learned, it is being done by a monomaniac with a mission."</Text>
    <Author>Peter Drucker</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="17">
    <Text>"The greatest danger for most of us is not that our aim is too high and we miss it, but that it is too low and we reach it."</Text>
    <Author>Michelangelo</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="18">
    <Text>"The mind is its own place, and in itself can make heaven of hell, or a hell of heaven"</Text>
    <Author>John Milton</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="19">
    <Text>"Enlightened trial and error outperforms the planning of flawless intellects"</Text>
    <Author>David Kelly</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="20">
    <Text>"Thousands of candles can be lit from a single candle, and the life of the candle will not be shortened. Happiness never decreases by being shared"</Text>
    <Author>The Buddha</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="21">
    <Text>"According to the laws of aerodynamics, a bumblebee cannot fly. The bumblebee doesn't know aerodynamics. So it flies anyway."</Text>
    <Author></Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="22">
    <Text>When you innovate, you've got to be prepared for everyone telling you you're nuts.</Text>
    <Author>Larry Ellison</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="23">
    <Text>Love like you've never been hurt and live like it's heaven on earth.</Text>
    <Author>Larry Ellison</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="24">
    <Text>"No individual can win a game by himself."</Text>
    <Author>Pele</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote id="25">
    <Text>"Outstanding leaders go out of their way to boost the selfesteem of their personnel. If people believe in themselves, it's amazing what they can accomplish."</Text>
    <Author>Sam Walton</Author>
  </Quote>
  </Quotes>
